breezepm.com 2011-07-19

# Breeze - Project Planning, Tracking, Collaboration & Delivery software and Tickets, Change Request Management Software

##### Privacy Policy

We keep record of each visitor’s email address and other information aggregated for survey or site registrations. The collection of information is solely used to improve the quality of our service and content of our web pages. We under no circumstances share or sell your information to other organizations for commercial purposes but only use it to provide products and services you’ve requested upon your permission. 

When you access breezepm, we may track your usage including date and time of visits, browser type, page visits, IP address, etc. We keep your information 100% private and confidential. However we may use your information for purposes below:

  * For authenticity to enable you to access breezepm. 
  * To inform you about any changes in the service, maintenance notifications, promotional materials and newsletters from breezepm.
  * To improve quality of our service and to track and determine troubles
  * To ask you for reviews on the website and your experience using breezepm
  * For billing related activities

##### When we will share your information?

  * We may share your information in the case of an investigation, fraudulent or illegal activities on the site, undesired activity involving possible threat to the safety of any person or our system and violation of terms of use.
  * We may transfer your information if breezepm is merged or acquired by another company. Under such an event, we will inform you before transferring your information. Once transferred, you will be subjected to a different privacy policy.

When you register for breezepm, you are asked to provide information like name, company name, email address, billing address and credit card information. However, free members are not required to enter the credit card details. We use the collected information for normal purposes like billing, product and service provision, authentication, research, contact and services improvement.

##### Security and data ownership

We undertake optimal security measures to safeguard your information from unauthorized. For data storage we take the help of third party vendors and hosting providers to give us essential infrastructure, software, hardware, networking, storage and other technology needed. We own all the codes and databases but as a customer, you will have rights to your data. We ensure complete protection of your data by not sharing or selling it to any third party for any purpose.

We may create a forum or blog platform for public discussion for people in which any information disclosed should be viewed as public information only and each user would be held responsible for exercising caution while disclosing any personal information.

We will not be responsible for any disclosed information or any action taken due to disclosed information.

##### Cookies

A cookie is usually information sent to your browser from the web server and stored on your PC. Breezepm uses cookies to store and track information but does not use permanent cookies. The user would be required to log-in to breezepm project after completion of the specified elapsed time to prevent illegal usage of the account by others.

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve full rights to change this privacy policy at point of time. We will thus inform you about significant changes occurred to our website by sending you mail on your primary email address.
